pricezombie.com 2014-06-07

# PriceZombie Privacy Policy

## PriceZombie Privacy Policy

Effective July 13, 2013 

This document is our Privacy Policy, which describes the information we collect and how it is used. This Privacy Policy applies to all interactions with PriceZombie.com. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. Your use of and/or registration with PriceZombie will constitute your agreement to our policy. If you cannot agree to the terms and conditions set forth below, please do not use our services. Additionally, our Privacy Policy is part of our User Agreement, and by using the site you agree to both. 

## About This Policy

PriceZombie is a comparison shopping and price tracking website, and includes an open platform for user comments. 

It is necessary for PriceZombie to collect some information so you can participate on the site. For example, registration and login, your product Watchlist, and our forums all depend on PriceZombie recognizing you and associating certain data with your account. From time to time we collect other information that is necessary to make the service work. 

PriceZombie utilizes third party web statistic software that provides general information about our userbase to help us determine which promotions and advertisements are effective. 

PriceZombie does not distribute, sell, or profit from information about our users. PriceZombie does not share information about our users unless we are legally compelled to do so. 

Please read this privacy policy carefully. It describes what information we collect, how it is used, and when it is shared so you can make smart decisions about how you use PriceZombie. 

## Registration Information

When you create an account, you are required to provide a username and password and an email address. We also log, and retain indefinitely, the IP address from which the account is initially created. This information allows you to login and be recognized as a member, have the forum posts you write be attributed to you, and it is necessary for your Watchlist to function. 

## Post, Content and Review Data

The posts, content, and reviews you make on PriceZombie are not private and remain on our servers even if your account is deleted. PriceZombie only saves the final version of what you post to our site. Previous edits are not available. 

## Log Data

Log data is certain information that is automatically collected by our systems when anyone visits PriceZombie. The data logged includes the type of software used to access the site (browser, operating system), the address of the external or internal page that referred you, and your IP address. 

## Your Private Information is Never For Sale

Unless compelled by law to divulge information, we do not sell or otherwise give access to any information collected about our users to any third party. Anonymous, aggregated information that cannot be linked back to an individual user may be made available to third parties in order to provide better services. For example, if data shows an increase in visitors from a special interest site, we may use that information to invite the participation of more stores that would interest that demographic. 

## PriceZombie Will Not Disclose Your Information

PriceZombie will not disclose your information unless required by law. We may disclose – or preserve for future disclosure – your information if we believe, after due consideration, that doing so is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation, or valid legal process. If we are going to release your information, we will do our best to provide you with notice in advance via PriceZombie's private messaging system unless we are prohibited by court order from doing so (e.g., an order under 18 U.S.C. § 2705(b)). 

## Cookie Policy

Cookies are small data files placed on your computer by websites you visit in order to help them remember certain information about you. At PriceZombie, we set only a few cookies for tracking user preferences, authentication, and collecting anonymous analytics data. Additionally, our advertising partners set cookies. Each of these uses is described in greater detail below. 

## Authentication Cookies

When you log into your account, PriceZombie will place a cookie for the sole purpose of creating this session. It contains your user id and hashed authentication information. 

## Analytics Cookies

We use a tool called Google Analytics to help us understand how users interact with our website. It tells us aggregate usage and traffic information, such as how the site was accessed, how long visitors stayed, and the number of first-time visitors to the site. By knowing how people use the site, we can make it better. To learn more about Google Analytics and how it uses your data, please visit <http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html>. 

## Diabling Cookies

Most browsers include an option to clear existing cookies or reject new ones. However, if you do this, portions of the PriceZombie website may not function as intended. 

## Data Security

PriceZombie will make every effort to secure any private information submitted to us by our users. However, data transmission over the internet can not be guaranteed secure, so use the service at your own risk. You are responsible for taking reasonable measures to secure your account (such as not sharing your computer or PriceZombie password, and using an up to date firewall and anti-virus software). 

## International Visitors

PriceZombie is a United States based company. All personal information we collect from our international users is transferred to the United States and processed according to US law. 

PriceZombie complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. PriceZombie has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view PriceZombie's certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>. 

## Children Under 13

Although we welcome users from all walks of life, our site is not aimed at children, and the United States government has put limits on our ability to accept users under a certain age through the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. Individuals under the age of 13 may not create an account with us. If you believe someone 12 or younger is using our site without parental consent, please contact us. 

## Changes To This Policy

We reserve the right to change this policy to meet the changing needs of PriceZombie, or for any other reason. If we make changes, we will notify our users. Where the changes substantially alters your rights, notice will appear prominently on your front page. More minor changes may only be highlighted by the privacy policy link in the footer of our website. 

Copyright © 2014 PriceZombie, LLC.
